<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richmond's Best Real Estate Training - Marc Highfill</title>
    <description>Marc Austin Highfill, a top Real Estate Agent in Richmond, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 14:36:07 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 14:36:07 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What You Need To Do in a Shifting Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DPDi8RgfIzw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A few ways to help you adapt to our rapidly changing real estate market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real estate market is shifting, and whether you’re new to the industry or an experienced agent, you need to know how to adapt. Today I want to share some tips that have helped my team remain successful throughout the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the best ways to continuously grow your business is to get back to basics.&lt;/strong&gt; Keep up with your sphere of influence and past clients. You might have to do more prospecting than you once did. You’ll have to talk to more people to find opportunities to grow your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I’ve seen recessions, booms, and everything between, and my team has grown through each change.%20http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-do-in-a-shifting-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I’ve seen recessions, booms, and everything between, and my team has grown through each change.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most important thing you can do to keep up with this market is to &lt;strong&gt;put yourself in an environment that encourages growth.&lt;/strong&gt; Be as knowledgeable and accountable as possible so that you’re an expert for your clients. Surround yourself with other industry professionals who discuss real-world situations and offer you advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been in this industry for over 20 years. I’ve seen recessions, booms, and everything between, and through each of those changes, my team has managed to become more and more profitable each time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in learning more about adapting to our changing market, call or email us today. We’d love to help you identify what you can do to become more successful. Remember, it’s not the market, it’s the marketing that makes the difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-do-in-a-shifting-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-do-in-a-shifting-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Agents Should Respond to This Shifting Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NqE4F5BHP0k?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;It’s up to real estate agents to be the calm in this stormy market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A market shift is on the horizon. Though economists are anticipating a recession, remember that a recession does not equal a housing crisis. What does this mean for you as a real estate agent? As experts in the real estate field, our No. 1 responsibility is to inform and educate our clients when a market shift occurs. We have to be the voice of reason providing facts and data to our clients. Let’s look at the data to put things into perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home values continued to appreciate during four of the last six recessions in the U.S.&lt;/strong&gt; Home values declined in the 1990s by less than 2%, and then again in 2008. Anyone who remembers the 2008 crash may think we’re headed that way again. However, it’s up to us to educate ourselves and our clients to ease those fears and help them understand what is actually happening and how it can affect their buying and selling decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Make sure your clients know you are the expert when it comes to a shifting market.%20http://localhost:4000/how-agents-should-respond-to-this-shifting-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Make sure your clients know you are the expert when it comes to a shifting market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market conditions are not the same as they were leading up to the 2008 crisis.&lt;/strong&gt; A shortage of inventory, tighter lending regulations, and lower interest rates all have contributed to the current market frenzy. Even if home appreciation starts to slow, there’s no indication it will decline. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure your clients know you are the expert when it comes to a shifting market. Share facts on social media, through videos, and in your newsletters. Connect with your past clients and your sphere of influence and ask them to share your content to reach more people. Don’t be afraid to have conversations about the market. Your friends and family will trust you as the expert if you are basing your conversations on facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have a more in-depth conversation about changing markets and what data you should be sharing with your clients, reach out to us by phone or email. Our coaches will share information to help you be the industry expert and keep your clients informed. And remember: It’s Not the Market…it’s the Marketing That Makes the Difference!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-agents-should-respond-to-this-shifting-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-agents-should-respond-to-this-shifting-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Agent FAQ's</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Tavian Anderson Became a Top Producer</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2TdeIIujAiE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;How EXIT First Realty agent Tavian Anderson found success in real estate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we’re joined by Tavian Anderson, an excellent real estate agent with EXIT First Realty. He joined us a year and a half ago, and we wanted to check in with him and see what he’s learned, how he’s been dealing with this wild real estate market, how he’s doing with his goals, and more. In April, he was one of our top producers, so we’re excited to speak to him today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feel free to watch the full message above or use these timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:00 — Introduction to today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:50 — The deals Tavian has closed and what his goals are&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:10 — The biggest challenge Tavian has faced working in real estate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:10 — How he’s helped first-time buyers who can’t offer extra incentives to sellers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:35 — The importance of having buyer consultations&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:45 — How coaching and masterminds have helped Tavian assist his clients&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:20 — What has helped his business grow the most&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:15 — How Tavian works with buyers who think they need to wait until the market crashes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12:30 — His advice for struggling agents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:45 — Wrapping up today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for Tavian or would like to speak to him about how he’s gotten his business where it is, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/tavian.anderson.77&quot;&gt;reach out to him on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, or call him at (804) 629-3769. You can also follow him on Instagram: @taytherealtor_. If you want to reach out to Sam Bingham about what we’re doing at EXIT First and how our coaching has helped agents like Tavian, reach out to her at (804) 527-3948 or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:samantha@marcshomes.net&quot;&gt;samantha@marcshomes.net&lt;/a&gt;. Remember, it’s not the market; it’s the marketing that makes the difference!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-tavian-anderson-became-a-top-producer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-tavian-anderson-became-a-top-producer.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Solution to Getting Buyers' Offers Accepted</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5z5b36ee008?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;All buyer’s agents should be doing this in our competitive market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I speak with agents every day who have the same issues: They’re struggling to get their buyers’ offers accepted in this challenging market. I’ve started diving deeper into why so many agents are struggling and what we can do to help change that. Today I’m excited to share that I’ve discovered a solution that has helped several agents win more deals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I recommend that you have a sit-down buyer presentation before showing them homes.&lt;/strong&gt; It sounds simple, and you might be thinking that it won’t really help, but here’s the thing: Most agents don’t have a solid plan for their clients. Instead, they just scramble to schedule the next showing without properly educating the buyers about the process and what kind of offers they should be making to win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You're the expert, and you have to prove that to your clients.%20http://localhost:4000/a-solution-to-convert-more-buyer-leads.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You’re the expert, and you have to prove that to your clients.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this initial meeting, you’re able to solely focus on your buyers and their specific needs. Then you can take the time to educate them on the process, the market, and the strategies they need to win. It doesn’t matter if your clients have bought a home in the past or not; &lt;strong&gt;by taking the time to understand their situation and explaining what you’ll do every day to help them buy a house, you’ll build trust.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once that trust is established, clients are more likely to take your advice when making offers. Provide data, facts, and success stories from past clients as well. You’re the expert, and you have to prove that to your clients to separate yourself from the competition. &lt;strong&gt;The only way to get clients prepared to make the necessary quick decisions in the market is to take time to get to know their needs and demonstrate your value.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about how to structure a buyer presentation to highlight your strengths, contact my team today for a free business strategy session. If you have any other questions about the real estate business, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. Remember, it’s not the market; it’s the marketing that makes the difference!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-solution-to-convert-more-buyer-leads.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-solution-to-convert-more-buyer-leads.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Way To Win More Listings</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RqgorjDxEsQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s how you can win listings in a low-inventory real estate market. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every week on my coaching calls, my agents ask me the same question: “How can I win more listings?” In a low-inventory market like this one, most agents are struggling to secure solid leads. However, my team has thrived in this environment. Today I want to share my secret for winning listings in this market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate is a tough industry. Everything runs on competition, and it’s easy to feel like you’re completely by yourself. I believe in doing things a different way. By sharing ideas and strategies, my team focuses on cooperation and making everyone better in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you use the same sales pitch at every listing appointment, you’ll just sound like every other agent. %20http://localhost:4000/the-best-way-to-win-more-listings.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you use the same sales pitch at every listing appointment, you’ll just sound like every other agent. ”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key to winning consistent listings is to give your sellers exit strategies. &lt;strong&gt;No two sellers are the same. &lt;/strong&gt;Some sellers want the most money possible no matter what. Others want good terms, extra moving time, or a quick sale. Because every seller is unique, you have to provide different solutions for their potential problems. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use the same sales pitch at every listing appointment, you’ll just sound like every other agent out there. &lt;strong&gt;You have to provide several exit strategies for your potential sellers.&lt;/strong&gt; This approach has allowed my team to stand out for years, but it has become even more valuable during this difficult market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to learn more about how you can provide exit strategies for your sellers, please call or email my team. My coaches will learn what makes you unique and help you craft a sales pitch based on your strengths. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-best-way-to-win-more-listings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-best-way-to-win-more-listings.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Agent Testimonial: Jon Witt</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/b383t47goOo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s our recent Q&amp;amp;A with Jon Witt, another important member of our team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recently sat down with another one of our great agents, Jon Witt, and had a chat about his experience in the real estate industry and with EXIT First Realty. Jon’s had great success working with EXIT and we want to share his story with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:00 — Introducing today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:41 — Life before real estate and why Jon got into this business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:00 — What attracted Jon to EXIT First Realty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:33 — Experience gained at EXIT First Realty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:45 — EXIT First Realty’s tools to help new agents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:08 — How being an EXIT agent changed Jon’s personal life&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:08 — Where Jon thinks he’d be right now if not for EXIT&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:11 — Looking to the future&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11:56 — Wrapping up&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to us by phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/agent-testimonial-jon-witt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/agent-testimonial-jon-witt.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How You Can Succeed in a Changing Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rSNSPclzbC8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;In a challenging market like this one, you need daily coaching to succeed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This real estate market is one of the toughest I’ve seen for buyers, and I’ve been in the business for a long time. Every buyer’s agent I speak with wants to know how they can be more successful in this market. They’re all coming up against the same obstacles as everyone else: low inventory and fierce competition. So what can you do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The secret is daily coaching over real-time situations.&lt;/strong&gt; Many agents aren’t getting the support and coaching they need to thrive in this market. It’s not easy to be an agent; you need to be knowledgeable and creative to close deals. If you aren’t surrounding yourself with industry experts who can help you adapt, you won’t be as successful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need coaches who have experience with real-life scenarios and market changes. These coaching sessions need to be frequent. Daily coaching is best, but weekly coaching is alright too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You don’t have to struggle alone in this competitive market.%20http://localhost:4000/how-you-can-succeed-in-a-changing-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You don’t have to struggle alone in this competitive market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market is changing rapidly, and you need to keep up. Unless you’ve been in this business for more than 10 years, you probably haven’t seen changes like we’re currently experiencing. &lt;strong&gt;You need to surround yourself with agents who can help you tackle everyday challenges&lt;/strong&gt; like getting creative with your offers, finding inventory in a seller’s market, winning listings with difficult sellers, managing rent-backs, handling appraisal waivers, and dealing with as-is inspections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t invent the scenarios we encounter as agents, so you need to find someone who is active in the business and succeeding despite the challenging market. &lt;strong&gt;Our coaches here at Exit First Realty offer free daily coaching to anyone interested.&lt;/strong&gt; You don’t even have to join our team!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to struggle alone; there are plenty of companies and agents who are willing to help. If you want to take advantage of our free coaching sessions, call us today. We’ll set up a free, no-obligation business strategy coaching session. We just want to help agents be successful so that our industry can grow and thrive. Remember, it’s not the market; it’s the marketing that makes the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 09:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-you-can-succeed-in-a-changing-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-you-can-succeed-in-a-changing-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Master Your Social Media Marketing</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/juLNsBDLaW0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Discussing five ways you can improve your social media marketing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the focus on social media in today’s world, if you’re not elevating your online presence, you’ll miss out on business. However, some agents find social media intimidating and don’t know where to start. Today I’ll give you five tips on mastering social media marketing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Just do it.&lt;/strong&gt; Whether you have an existing page or you’re just starting out, be prepared to learn and adapt. Many agents have the idea that everything needs to be perfect before posting. In reality, they just need to start doing and make changes as needed. You should first decide what you want your audience to take away from your account, then create a theme for your social media brand. This will help you formulate ideas for content to create. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Set boundaries.&lt;/strong&gt; Most people will be interested in your personal life, not just your real estate business. Social media is most successful when your goal is to connect to people, not just sell to them, so include content about your family, hobbies, and interests. However, you need to think about your limits and what parts of your life you’re not comfortable sharing. Keep in mind that extreme opinions about any topic on your social media may alienate potential clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Strive to be authentic and consistent.&lt;/strong&gt; Your photos and posts don’t have to be staged and perfect. Your audience will relate to you as a person. Don’t be afraid to share when you’re uncomfortable or nervous. Exposing those moments will make you engaging, and people will connect with you more. Consistency will help you maintain a presence and build trust. Find relatable things to post about at least three times a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your audience will relate to you as a person.%20http://localhost:4000/master-your-social-media-marketing.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your audience will relate to you as a person.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Evaluate and repeat.&lt;/strong&gt; Get comfortable asking and receiving feedback from your followers. No one expects you to get everything right from the start. Learn what your audience is connecting with, then repeat similar content to increase that connection. Pay attention to what time of day you’re getting the best engagement and try to post on that schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Be a storyteller.&lt;/strong&gt; Tell the story behind your photos and clients. This helps your audience resonate with the experience of buying or selling a home and what your business is like behind the scenes. Be proud of your accomplishments and share why they make your career worthwhile. This helps create that genuine connection that will make people want to work with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to further discuss how to increase your social media presence, contact my team by phone or email for a free business strategy session. Our coaches will help you create a social media strategy that achieves your goals and boosts your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 09:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/master-your-social-media-marketing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/master-your-social-media-marketing.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Proper Planning Prevents Poor Performance</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/SbvXka4BIIc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you want to increase the success of your business, plan ahead.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All highly successful people plan their days in advance. The more precise your planning is, the more successful you’ll be. &lt;strong&gt;Time blocking is a great way to start;&lt;/strong&gt; all you have to do is create your schedule by blocking out times for certain activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if you block two hours in the morning for prospecting, you need to plan exactly what lead sources you’ll call during that time. You could, say, block out the hour between 10 a.m. and 11 a.m. for calling internet leads like Zillow or Realtor.com. Then you could block the hour between 11 a.m. and noon to call past clients or your sphere of influence. With your past clients and sphere, make sure you write down the exact names of the people you’re calling so that you’re keeping a continuous rotation of connection with your clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use the same formula for every block of time in your calendar&lt;/strong&gt;, including time for marketing activities, showings, listing/buyer appointments, etc. Also, make sure to include a block for follow-up time. For many agents, the issue isn’t a lack of leads but rather a lack of follow-up. We all speak to people who tell you to call them next week or that they’ll call you in a couple of days. Take a minute to go forward to that time in your calendar and create a “heard from” category for your follow-up. Then, write that person’s name down in your “follow-up” block so that you know to touch base when you said you would. That helps to ensure that leads don’t fall through the cracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=All highly successful people plan their days in advance.%20http://localhost:4000/proper-planning-prevents-poor-performance.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“All highly successful people plan their days in advance.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter what kind of calendar you use—whether it’s a high-tech internet calendar or an old school calendar book (like mine)—writing down precisely what you are going to do and when you are going to do it will increase your success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking time every evening to plan your next day in advance will help you stay on track with your goals, and it will alleviate stress.&lt;/strong&gt; You won’t have to worry about what you’re going to do to get business every morning because you’ve already put a plan in place the night before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in learning more about how to plan your day or you have any questions, contact us today for a free business planning call. Just click on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://richmondrealestatejobs.com/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;“Business Strategy Call”&lt;/a&gt; button on our website. Our coaches will work to create a system of planning that works best for your business and your goals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/proper-planning-prevents-poor-performance.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/proper-planning-prevents-poor-performance.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Planning for 2022?  Get a Jumpstart Now</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zj6WO1qgHic?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s how to get a head start on your business as we roll into 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to succeed in 2022, &lt;strong&gt;the first quarter determines your success&lt;/strong&gt;. You should already be putting a plan in place now; that way you can be ahead of the game once the new year starts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve spoken with many agents during my coaching sessions who wait until the new year starts before creating a plan to increase their business.  While that’s never a bad time to put a plan in place, I encourage everyone to start before the new year begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your success in the first quarter will help determine your success for the rest of the year.%20http://localhost:4000/planning-for-2022-get-a-jumpstart-now.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your success in the first quarter will help determine your success for the rest of the year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think about the end of this year and the beginning of next year as just another quarter.  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://richmondrealestatejobs.com/set-yourself-up-for-real-estate-success-with-these-tips.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;As you may have seen in one of my previous videos&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; it’s critical to set quarterly goals to maintain your momentum throughout the year. If you want to be successful in 2022, setting and implementing a plan for the first quarter NOW is imperative. Your success in the first quarter will help determine your success for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, make sure to &lt;strong&gt;create specific action steps to achieve your goals&lt;/strong&gt;, then implement those action steps so that when the new year comes, you are already working on your plan. No matter what you want to achieve in 2022, you can make it happen by creating a plan, having an accountability partner, and measuring your activities or progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to meet with one of our coaches for a FREE business planning session to help you create a strategy for 2022, or if you have any questions, give us a call or send us an email. Our coaches will go over your goals, help you determine where you were most successful this year, and help you create a plan with action steps so you can achieve the success you want next year. We will also help keep you accountable and make sure you stay on track. We hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/planning-for-2022-get-a-jumpstart-now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/planning-for-2022-get-a-jumpstart-now.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
