<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Richmond Real Estate Podcast with Marc Austin Highfill</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Marc Austin Properties - your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Marc Austin Highfill</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-06-15 13:53:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Marc Austin Highfill</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>marc@marcshomes.net</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Marc Austin Highfill</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Marc Austin Highfill</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Richmond Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Marc Austin Properties - your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Time Block</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-time-block.html</link>
        
        <author>Marc Austin Highfill</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-31 10:15:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Marc+Highfill/How+to+Time+Block.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are some time blocking tips that will help you be more successful.

The key to being more successful is time blocking and time management. How do you manage your time efficiently and utilize time blocking?

First, you must use a calendar system. Whether it’s a calendar book or Google Calendar, you need a calendar you’ll use every day. 

Once you have a calendar, it’s time to schedule your “rocks.” These are the most important things that must be done every day, like prospecting, showing appointments, inspections, etc. These things are non-negotiable—don’t interfere with them. 

You should prospect for at least two hours, and your prospecting goal is to schedule appointments. If you’re prospecting for one hour, prospect hard and fast for 50 minutes and then take a 10-minute break. If you need to check your phone, get up and walk around, or do anything else you need to do to keep your energy up, do it during this break. The next hour, do the exact same thing. 

“The secret to keeping a disciplined calendar is holding yourself accountable to all scheduled activities.”

When scheduling your prospecting time, you must also schedule who you’ll call specifically. This is something a lot of agents forget to do. You should know who you’ll call ahead of time so that when you’re in your prospecting zone, you’re focused and getting calls done left and right. You’d be amazed how many calls you can make by doing this. 

Also, don’t turn your calendar into a to-do list, where you have appointments and other things scheduled back to back all day long. You need to schedule breaks in between. 

What does all of this mean? Some experienced agents don’t use disciplined calendars day to day, week to week. They end up being reactive instead of proactive and don’t get the most important prospecting activities done. 

The secret to keeping a disciplined calendar is holding yourself accountable to all scheduled activities. On my team, our system involves a daily and weekly scorecard. If we maintain our daily successes throughout each week, we get a good score. That’s a direct indication of future business and success.

If you’d like to know more about our time blocking system, don’t hesitate to call our office and book a strategy session. If you have any other questions, feel free to reach out to me as well. Cheers to your business!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Marc+Highfill/How+to+Time+Block.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Marc+Highfill/How+to+Time+Block.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are some time blocking tips that will help you be more successful.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Marc Austin Highfill</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are some time blocking tips that will help you be more successful.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Generate More Referrals?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-generate-more-referrals.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Marc Austin Highfill</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-13 13:36:47 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Marc+Highfill/How+Can+You+Generate+More+Referrals_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Repeat clients and referrals are one of the most reliable sources of business. Here’s what you need to do to make this a pillar of yours.

If you want to generate more referral business from your past clients and sphere of influence, here are the things you must be doing:

1. You need to have a CRM and database. Which CRM is the best to use? The one that you use. It’s best to have one centrally located database, too. I’ve talked to some agents who’ve used Follow Up Boss, Boomtown, and Top Producer who have all had success. It’s important to keep that database in one place, add to it every day, and make sure everyone you know is in there. 

“It’s important to stay in touch and always provide value.”

2. Reach out to your database at least once a month. Each of our agents has a system set up to do this. It can be a text, email, phone call, or even a postcard. However, don’t use the same contact method twice in a row. Make sure these touches are scheduled in your calendar, too. It sounds easy, but I run across experienced agents every day who aren’t doing this.

3. Provide value. I hear from agents all the time who hesitate to reach out to their database because they don’t know what to bring in terms of value. It can be as easy as providing the latest market numbers or listings for buyers, or quarterly stats and a home value estimate for sellers. By staying in touch and letting them know you bring value, you’ll be considered a market expert.

For past clients who aren’t buying or selling right now, you want to be a resource by providing helpful, educational content. You can’t be what I call a “secret agent.” I see too many agents forget their past clients after helping them through a transaction. By keeping in touch with these people, you can earn their business over and over.

With these three tips, I guarantee that you’ll get more referral business. Just stay in touch regularly and provide value. If you’d like more specific tips, just give me a call or send an email. I would love to help you take your business to the next level.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Marc+Highfill/How+Can+You+Generate+More+Referrals_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Marc+Highfill/How+Can+You+Generate+More+Referrals_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Repeat clients and referrals are one of the most reliable sources of business. Here’s what you need to do to make this a pillar of yours.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Marc Austin Highfill</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Repeat clients and referrals are one of the most reliable sources of business. Here’s what you need to do to make this a pillar of yours.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Are You Being A Secret Agent?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-you-being-a-secret-agent.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Marc Austin Highfill</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-13 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What’s the easiest way to get more leads? Don’t be a secret agent. 

To show you what I mean by that, let me tell you about how we do business at Exit First Realty.

We coach our agents on how to find and generate different leads every day. We start by creating awareness that you’re in the real estate business. It could be something like wearing name tags or sticking signs on your car. Even your social media account is tagged. We also teach you how to build a database and contact that database to make sure everyone in it knows about the services you provide. 

This might sound basic, but you’d be surprised how many experienced agents don’t do these things. We have a proven system, with dialogues, that can turn everyday conversations into business. 

After you establish this foundation, we help you with your lead generation methods. What are the best open house dialogues? How do you convert internet leads? What other internet lead sources can you use to generate more leads?

I’ve also had good luck with agents getting involved with an area of interest to themselves that they can network through the group. For example, we had an agent who was a horse-riding enthusiast join a horse-riding club. She got a lot of business from them, but it also helped the group in a variety of ways. She was able to volunteer and get business from like-minded people just by doing what she loved. 

“Don’t be a secret agent.”

The point is, you have to let everyone know you work in real estate. We coach because coaching should be ongoing, just like the martial arts belt display you see behind me in the video above. I’ve practiced martial arts for roughly 20 years, and I’ve realized that real estate training is often just like martial arts training: Just like the belt system, you have to learn what to do step by step. We’ve applied this system to our office. No matter what “belt level” you are as an agent, you’re required to help other people. The belts aren’t there to show off; they’re there to demonstrate how to work each day. 

If you have any other questions, feel free to call or email me. I’d love to speak with you.

P.S. We’d love to see you at our upcoming networking event. If you or someone you know is looking to get into real estate or grow your real estate career, come learn about who we are, what we do, and the people behind our business. You can register for the event right here.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>It’s a question I hear all the time from agents looking to switch real estate companies: “How do I get more leads?” Usually, they aren’t looking for more leads—they’re just looking for an easy fix to get more business. There are multiple ways to produce more leads, but today I’ll reveal the easiest way. To find out more, watch this short video.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Marc Austin Highfill</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>It’s a question I hear all the time from agents looking to switch real estate companies: “How do I get more leads?” Usually, they aren’t looking for more leads—they’re just looking for an easy fix to get more business. There are multiple ways to produce more leads, but today I’ll reveal the easiest way. To find out more, watch this short video.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Marc Austin Highfill's Real Estate Journey</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/marc-austin-highfills-real-estate-journey.html</link>
        
        <author>Marc Austin Highfill</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-13 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Hear how Marc Austin Highfill got started in the real estate business, how he overcame the struggles in the early years, and his vision for the future.


</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Hear how Marc Austin Highfill got started in the real estate business, how he overcame the struggles in the early years, and his vision for the future.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Marc Austin Highfill</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Hear how Marc Austin Highfill got started in the real estate business, how he overcame the struggles in the early years, and his vision for the future.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Richmond, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Marc Austin Highfill</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Marc Austin Highfill</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Marc Austin Properties - your professional Richmond Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
